- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
kids: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
孩子们：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
[flute plays]
[长笛演奏]
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
♪ ♪
- Look, all I'm saying is there
are rules to surviving horror,
- 看，我要说的都在那里
是恐怖生存的规则，
like to go off alone, don't
say "I'll be right back,"
喜欢一个人走，不
说“我马上回来”
and no canoodling.
也不许亲热。
- And don't be ridiculous.
- 别开玩笑了。
You're all acting like
a bunch of babies.
你们都表现得像
一群婴儿。
I'm not afraid of any creature
or axe murderer or whatever.
我不惧怕任何生物
或斧头杀人犯或其他什么。
If anything scary came at me,
I'd hit 'em like this,
如果有什么可怕的事情向我袭来
我会这样打他们
and I'd hit 'em like that!
我会那样打他们！
- Bleh!
- 哎呀！
- [yelps]
- [尖叫声]
[laughter]
[笑声]
Very funny, Karen.
非常有趣，凯伦。
Very funny.
很搞笑。
Come on, chuckles.
来吧，笑声。
Let's blow this weenie
roast and canoodle.
让我们吹这个威尼
烤和煮。
- I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
- 我不会做
如果我是你。
- You wouldn't do anything
I would do, weirdo.
- 你什么也不会做
我愿意，怪人。
- Mmm.
- 嗯。
S'mores.
羊肚菌。
- You know that's
a pine cone, right?
- 你知道那是
松果，对吗？
- S'more pine cone for me!
- 给我更多松果！
[burps]
Mmm.
[打嗝]
嗯。
Spicy little devil.
麻辣小恶魔。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- Ugh!
- 呃！
Maybe we should
tell stories to keep
也许我们应该
讲故事以保留
our minds off the terrifying
horror that lurks in the dark.
我们的思想远离了可怕的事情
潜伏在黑暗中的恐怖。
- Ooh, I'll start.
- 哦，我要开始了。
It was a night just like
tonight, in an old abandoned
那是一个夜晚，就像
今晚，在一处废弃的旧屋里
camp just like this one.
就像这个营地一样。
But there was something
out there, something spooky
但有件事
那里有一些令人毛骨悚然的东西
that prowled in the woods.
在树林里徘徊的。
- Seriously?
- 严重地？
A scary camping story?
一个可怕的露营故事？
- It's the only story
I can remember right now.
- 这是唯一的故事
我现在就记得。
- Ooh, tell the part with
all the bloody axe-murdering!
- 哦，告诉这部分
所有该死的斧头谋杀！
Both: No!
两人：不！
- All right, that's it!
- 好吧，就是这样！
No more campfire.
不再有篝火。
We're all going to stay
together in the old Dingy Cabin
我们都会留下来
一起在肮脏的旧小屋里
until morning.
直到早上。
- Good idea.
- 好主意。
I'll go get Plankton and Karen.
我去去找浮游生物和凯伦。
I'll be right back.
我马上回来。
- She's dead.
- 她死了。
- Aw.
- 噢。
Our old cabin.
我们的旧小屋。
It's a fixer-upper.
这是一个固定鞋面。
- More like a tearer-downer.
- 更像是催泪弹。
- I call top bunk.
- 我打电话给上铺。
[door squeaks]
[门吱吱作响]
- SpongeBob, I think
there's someone
- 海绵宝宝，我想
有人
sleeping in this bunk bed.
睡在这张双层床上。
[all whimpering]
[全都呜咽]
- [yelps]
- [尖叫声]
[sea urchins growling]
[海胆咆哮]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[sea urchins
imitating conga line chant]
[海胆
模仿康加线圣歌]
- [imitating conga line chant]
- [模仿康加线圣歌]
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
- [panting] Can I faint now?
- [气喘吁吁]我现在可以晕倒吗？
- Be my guest.
- 做我的客人。
- [gasping]
- [喘气]
- Uh, what do I do with this?
- 呃，我该怎么办？
[wolves howling]
[狼嚎]
[kissing noises]
[接吻声]
- Whoo!
- 呼！
Yes!
是的！
I made it to first base!
我到达一垒了！
[electronic beeping]
[电子蜂鸣声]
Huh?
啊？
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
- Oh, there you are.
- 哦，你来了。
Hello.
你好。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- What is wrong with you?
- 你怎么了？
I almost had a heart attack!
我差点心脏病发作！
And what's with the mask?
面具又是怎么回事？
- Oh, don't be so dramatic.
-哦，别这么戏剧化。
I just found some of my old
hockey equipment in the woods.
我刚刚找到了一些旧的
树林里的曲棍球设备。
It's still got my name on it.
上面仍然有我的名字。
Good times.
美好时光。
[both yelp]
[两人都尖叫]
- Plankton?
- 浮游生物？
Karen?
凯伦？
Come on, I know you're
just trying to scare me.
来吧，我知道你是
只是想吓唬我。
Holy Zamboni!
圣赞博尼！
[shrieks]
[尖叫声]
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- All right, so where was I?
- 好吧，那我刚才说到哪儿了？
Oh, yeah, I remember now.
哦，是的，我现在想起来了。
There was something
spooky out there
有东西
外面很诡异
prowling around in the woods.
在树林里徘徊。
And it made a terrifying shriek!
并且发出了恐怖的惨叫声！
[clarinet screeching]
[单簧管尖叫声]
[all whimpering]
[全都呜咽]
- Ugh!
- 呃！
I'm tired of being scared.
我厌倦了害怕。
- Me too.
- 我也是。
Both: Me too.
两人：我也是。
- Uh, I'm not tired
of being scared yet.
- 呃，我不累
还害怕。
- Come on, fellers.
- 来吧，伙计们。
It's time we fought back!
我们是时候反击了！
[clarinet screeching]
[单簧管尖叫声]
- [yelps]
The... Creeper.
- [尖叫声]
……爬行者。
♪ ♪
- Hi-yah!
- 嗨呀！
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- Ohh!
- 哦！
[groans]
[呻吟]
[together]
Squidward?
[一起]
章鱼哥？
Ow!
噢！
All: Patrick.
全体：帕特里克.
- At least Squidward's safe.
- 至少章鱼哥安全了。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- Ow!
- 噢！
You guys?
你们？
What are you idiots doing here?
你们这些白痴在这里做什么？
- We're here
for the Kamp Koral reunion.
- 我们在这里
参加 Kamp Koral 聚会。
Aren't you?
- Reunion?
你不是吗？
- 重聚？
No.
不。
I've been here for a week ever
since I was banned from playing
我已经在这里呆了一个星期了
自从我被禁止玩游戏以来
clarinet in Bikini Bottom.
比基尼泳裤中的单簧管。
- The city has been
rather peaceful lately.
- 这座城市已经
最近比较平静。
- Didn't you notice
that I haven't
- 你没注意到吗
我还没有
been at work for a whole week?
已经工作了一整周？
- I assumed you were
just on a bathroom break.
- 我以为你是
刚刚上厕所休息。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- You must have
gotten an invite.
- 你必须有
收到了邀请。
- Hold on.
- 坚持，稍等。
I believe this is yours.
我相信这是你的。
- Huh.
[clam squawking]
- 嗯。
[蛤蜊叫声]
This letter is for
Old Man Walker.
这封信是为了
沃克老人。
He never even went to this camp.
他甚至从未去过这个营地。
You idiots ruined
my perfect getaway.
你们这些白痴毁了
我的完美假期。
Now I have to get away
again, all over again.
现在我必须离开
再次，一切重来。
Ow!
噢！
[sighs]
Typical.
[叹气]
典型的。
[sputters]
[溅射声]
- No!
Wait!
- 不！
等待！
Don't go out alone.
不要一个人出去。
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
It's too late.
太晚了。
He's vanished.
他失踪了。
- Everybody's vanished.
- 大家都消失了。
- Everybody?
- 大家？
Ah!
啊!
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Help, I'm vanishing!
救命啊，我快消失了！
- Come on, Patrick.
- 来吧，帕特里克。
Materialize.
实现。
Are you OK, buddy?
你还好吗，伙计？
- I don't know.
- 我不知道。
I'm still processing.
我还在处理中。
- Squidward was taken because
he ignored the rules of horror.
- 章鱼哥被带走是因为
他无视恐怖规则。
- You mean, don't wear
white after Labor Day?
- 你的意思是，不穿
劳动节后变白？
- Ugh!
- 呃！
I repeat,
don't go off alone, don't say,
我再说一遍，
不要一个人走，不要说
I'll be right back,
and absolutely no canoodling.
我马上回来，
绝对不能亲热。
Watch.
手表。
I'll prove it.
我会证明这一点。
[makes kissing noises]
[发出接吻声]
Oh, my pumpkin.
哦，我的南瓜。
My little lump of sugar.
我的小糖块。
Sweet honey pie.
甜甜的蜂蜜馅饼。
- Did he say "honey pie"?
- 他说的是“蜂蜜派”吗？
I'm hungry.
我饿了。
- [kissing]
- [接吻]
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Augh.
- 噢。
All: Oh.
全体：哦。
- And that's why
you don't canoodle.
- 这就是为什么
你不会亲热。
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Stand back, y'all.
- 退后一点，你们。
Hi-yah!
嗨呀！
Whoever it is,
they're probably still close.
不管是谁，
他们可能还很接近。
Let's get 'em.
让我们抓住他们。
- [grumbling] Ugh, there must
be somewhere I can play without
- [抱怨] 呃，一定有
是我可以在没有的情况下玩耍的地方
any annoying interruptions.
任何烦人的打扰。
Huh?
啊？
You imbeciles better
not be following me!
你个傻逼更好
别跟着我！
[sighs]
[叹气]
Those morons got me all jumpy.
那些白痴让我浑身紧张。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Huh?
啊？
[both boinging]
[双方都在轰鸣]
I hate to admit it,
but that's pretty cute.
我不愿意承认，
但这很可爱。
[bunnies giggling]
[兔子咯咯地笑]
- Ow!
- 噢！
I take it back!
我收回来！
Bad bunnies!
坏兔子们！
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
Huh?
All right, who is it now?
啊？
好吧，现在是谁？
I have a clarinet,
and I'm not afraid to use it.
我有一支单簧管
我并不害怕使用它。
[clarinet blares]
[单簧管的声音]
Guess I blew them away.
猜猜我把他们吹走了。
[laughing]
[笑]
[shrieks]
[尖叫声]
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Squidward!
- 章鱼哥！
Harvey!
哈维！
- Mrs. Puff?
- 帕夫夫人？
Mo?
莫？
- Lady Upturn?
- 女士崛起？
Daddy?
爸爸？
- I'm hollering!
- 我在喊叫！
I'm yelling!
我大喊大叫！
[laid-back clarinet music]
[悠闲的单簧管音乐]
- Did you hear that?
- 你听到了吗？
Clarinet music.
单簧管音乐。
It must be Squidward.
一定是章鱼哥。
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Aw, it's just a snail.
- 噢，这只是一只蜗牛。
- Yeah, I thought
it sounded too good.
- 是的，我想
听起来太好了。
- I'll keep this safe until we
can give it back to Squidward.
- 我会保管好这个直到我们
可以把它还给章鱼哥。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
I doubt he'll want it back now.
我怀疑他现在会想要回来。
- [sighs] I'm beat.
- [叹气]我被打败了。
I think we should call off
the search until morning.
我想我们应该取消
搜索一直到早上。
[gasps]
Guys!
[喘气]
伙计们！
Guys!
It got me.
它抓住了我。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[screams]
Help!
[尖叫声]
救命啊！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
- She's gone!
- Oh!
- 她走了！
- 哦！
The Creeper's got her.
爬行者抓住了她。
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- Now it's got Patrick!
- 现在帕特里克来了！
- It's coming from back there!
- 它是从后面传来的！
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- The old Trawler cabin!
- 旧拖网渔船小屋！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- Patrick?
- 帕特里克？
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
- What is up?
- 怎么了？
- Was that you yelling?
- 是你在喊吗？
- Yelling?
Oh!
- 大喊大叫？
哦！
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Uh, I wanted
to warn you about, um...
呃，我想要
警告你，嗯...
- This spiderweb?
- 这个蜘蛛网？
- Uh, yeah!
- 呃，是的！
- Aw, thanks, buddy.
- 噢，谢谢，伙计。
[roaring]
[咆哮]
[all whimpering]
[全都呜咽]
- On the count of three, boys.
- 数到三，孩子们。
1, 2, 3!
1、2、3！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- [gasps] Of all the
screamers back in the day,
- [喘气] 在所有的
当年的尖叫声，
you guys were the best.
你们是最棒的。
- Huh?
- 啊？
Big and Lil Roxie?
大罗克西和小罗克西？
Or is it Little and Big Roxie?
或者是小洛克西和大洛克西？
- Y'all switched places?
- 你们都换地方了？
- It happens every
three moon cycles.
- 它发生在每个
三个月亮周期。
- Turnabout is fair play.
- 逆转是公平竞争。
- [sputtering]
- [溅射]
- Good evening, everyone.
- 大家晚上好。
Welcome to my parlor.
欢迎来到我的客厅。
Snip! Snip! Snip!
剪断！剪断！剪断！
- Howdy, Preda Tory.
- 你好，普雷达·托里。
[thunder crashes]
[雷霆轰鸣]
[all yelp]
[大家尖叫]
[eerie organ music]
[诡异的管风琴音乐]
- [screeching]
- [尖叫声]
[hisses]
[嘶嘶声]
- Kidferatu!
- 基德费拉图！
All grown up.
都长大了。
Good to see you're
still dead and well.
很高兴看到你
仍然死了而且很好。
- [hisses]
- [嘶嘶声]
- He's a count now.
- 他现在是伯爵了
[squelching]
[压抑]
- It's great
to see you guys again.
- 太棒了
再次见到你们。
- Jimmy Blobfish?
- 吉米水滴鱼？
You look...
你看起来...
- Yeah, I know.
- 是的，我知道。
I know.
我知道。
I lost my looks.
我失去了容貌。
I was much cuter
when I was young.
我更可爱
当我年轻的时候。
- It's the delicious
insides that count.
- 这就是美味
重要的内部。
- [munching]
- [咀嚼]
Yeah, but his outside
isn't so bad, either.
是的，但是他的外面
也不错。
He still tastes
like maple syrup.
他还是有味道
像枫糖浆。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
I almost forgot.
我差点忘了。
We're all in danger.
我们都处于危险之中。
There's a Creeper in camp.
营地里有一只苦力怕。
- A Creeper?
- 爬行者？
- Sounds like
our kind of people.
- 听起来像
我们这样的人。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
- Y'all don't understand.
- 你们都不明白。
He's been snatching up everyone
who's here for the reunion.
他已经把所有人都抢走了
谁来这里参加聚会。
- This Creeper
sounds fascinating.
- 这个爬行者
听起来很有趣。
- What do we gotta
do to get snatched?
- 我们要做什么
被抢怎么办？
- Well, Harvey said
you have to break
- 哈维说
你必须打破
one of the rules of horror.
恐怖规则之一。
- That's easy.
- 这很容易。
We know them all.
我们都认识他们。
[together]
Ahh! Run!
[一起]
啊！跑步！
- What are you doing?
- 你在干什么？
- We'll be right back.
- 我们马上回来。
- [hisses]
- [嘶嘶声]
[together]
Hooray!
[一起]
万岁！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
They're gone.
他们走了。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
I got it!
我得到了它！
I know who the Creeper is.
我知道爬行者是谁。
Think about it.
想一想。
Who used to prank us
all the time?
谁曾经恶作剧我们
一直吗？
Both: Hmm.
两人：嗯。
- Our old hill folk
friends, Narlene and Nobby!
- 我们的老山民
朋友们，纳琳和诺比！
Both: Ohh.
两人：哦。
- So I say it's time
for us to prank them back.
- 所以我说是时候了
让我们恶作剧回来。
- Narlene's cabin
looks abandoned.
- 纳琳的小屋
看起来被遗弃了。
- That's how it always looks.
- 看起来总是如此。
It's shack chic.
这是小屋别致。
They're in there.
他们就在那里。
I can feel it in my tail.
我可以在我的尾巴上感觉到它。
- I can taste it in your tail.
- 我可以在你的尾巴里尝到它的味道。
[spits]
[吐口水]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[both snoring]
[两人都打呼噜]
- You got your pie?
- 你有馅饼吗？
- It's here, in my pie hole.
- 就在这里，在我的馅饼洞里。
- When Patrick wakes them
up with the clarinet,
- 当帕特里克叫醒他们时
与单簧管一起，
let 'em have it.
让他们拥有吧。
- [inhales deeply]
- [深吸一口气]
[clarinet blaring]
[单簧管的声音]
- Why didn't that work?
- 为什么那不起作用？
Dummies?
傻瓜？
Both: Grrr.
两人：呃。
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
- Huh?
- 啊？
Whoa!
哇！
- More decoys?
- 更多诱饵？
- Patrick!
- 帕特里克！
Help us.
帮助我们。
- I got it.
- 我得到了它。
[licking]
[舔]
- Patrick?
- 帕特里克？
[sighs]
Nobby, cut 'em down.
[叹气]
诺比，砍倒他们。
[both grunt, groan]
[两人咕哝，呻吟]
- Hoo-wee!
- 呼威！
If'n it ain't the old
ding dong Dinghies.
如果不是旧的
叮咚小艇。
What y'all doing
in our domicile?
你们在做什么
在我们的住所？
- Like you don't know!
- 就像你不知道一样！
You've been pranking
us all night!
你一直在恶作剧
我们整个晚上！
- Ha!
- 哈！
'Fraid not.
恐怕不会。
We've been busy trying to
catch a critter that's been
我们一直在忙着尝试
抓住一只已经被
trespassing on our property.
侵入我们的财产。
That's why we rigged
the booby trap.
这就是我们操纵的原因
诱杀装置
- Alas, the only boobies
we caught were you.
- 唉，唯一的胸部
我们抓住的是你。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- I bet it was the Creeper.
- 我打赌那是苦力怕。
He invited us to a camp reunion,
他邀请我们参加营地聚会，
only to snatch everybody away.
只为抢走所有人。
- How would you all
like to team up with us
- 你们会怎样
喜欢与我们合作
and put a stop to this varmint?
并阻止这个害虫？
- Does the tin-man have
a sheet-metal behind?
- 铁皮人有吗
后面有金属板吗？
Time we armed up!
是时候我们武装起来了！
[twangy banjo music]
[班卓琴音乐]
- [grunts] Ha-ha!
- [咕哝]哈哈！
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Heh-heh-heh-heh-heh.
嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿。
♪ ♪
[together]
Ha-ha!
[一起]
哈哈！
- [chomps]
- [咀嚼]
- Patrick!
- 帕特里克！
Don't eat your weapon.
别吃你的武器。
- Whoo-hoo!
- 呼呼！
Let's catch us a Creeper.
让我们抓住一只苦力怕吧。
- [babbles]
- [胡言乱语]
[munching]
[咀嚼]
[bird squawking]
[鸟叫声]
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
[all whimpering]
[全都呜咽]
- What is that sound?
- 那是什么声音？
- [gulps] Don't worry, guys.
- [吞咽]别担心，伙计们。
I'll protect you
with my sandwich.
我会保护你
和我的三明治。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[yelps]
Oh, no, my sandwich!
[尖叫声]
哦，不，我的三明治！
[stammering]
[结巴]
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
Oh.
哦。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
[gasps]
[喘气]
- Oh, no.
- 哦，不。
That's Patrick.
那是帕特里克。
He's been snatched.
他被抢走了。
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
[all whimpering]
[全都呜咽]
- Whatever's out
there's going to get us.
- 无论发生什么
会有人来抓我们的。
- That leaves us
only one option.
- 那只剩下我们了
只有一个选择。
- Run!
- 跑步！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- No!
- 不！
I was going to say fight back!
我本来想说反击！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Sugar Squeezin'.
榨糖啦
Huh?
啊？
[babbling]
[胡说]
For courage.
为了勇气。
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Need more courage.
- 需要更多的勇气。
[glugging]
[咕噜咕噜]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
That Creeper'll never catch me
in my underground tree
那个苦力怕永远抓不到我
在我的地下树里
stump system.
树桩系统。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[grunts] Huh?
[咕哝]嗯？
I'm caught.
我被抓住了。
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
[thunder crashing]
[雷霆轰鸣]
[birds squawking]
[鸟儿的叫声]
- Stand back!
- 往后站！
I got an electro hammer,
and I'm not afraid to use it!
我有电锤，
我不害怕使用它！
Huh.
呵呵。
[sputtering]
[溅射]
My hammer's gone haywire!
我的锤子失控了！
Time for plan B.
是时候实施 B 计划了。
So long, Creeper!
再见，爬行者！
Whoa!
哇！
[sighs[ Now I know
what a balloon feels like.
[叹气[现在我知道了
气球是什么感觉。
The Clampitheater?
钳形剧场？
Is that where you've been
hiding all the bodies?
那是你去过的地方吗
隐藏所有尸体？
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Why are you doing this?
- 你为什么要这样做？
- Because...
this is fun.
- 因为...
这很有趣。
- Elwood?
- 埃尔伍德？
- Hi, Sandy.
- 嗨，桑迪。
- I always wondered
what happened to you.
- 我一直想知道
你发生了什么事。
- It was all those years ago.
——那都是很多年前的事了。
I missed the last bus
home from Kamp Koral
我错过了末班车
坎普·科拉尔的家
on the last day of camp.
在营地的最后一天。
Yay!
耶！
And I've been living
here alone ever since.
而我一直生活在
从此以后就独自一人在这里。
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
[straining]
[紧张]
It's been fun.
这很有趣。
[chomps]
[咀嚼]
Mmm.
嗯。
[yawns]
[哈欠]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
But I missed all you guys.
但我想念你们所有人。
[roars]
[怒吼]
Then one day, I thought,
if I throw a reunion,
然后有一天，我想，
如果我举办一次聚会，
everyone would come
back to Kamp Koral,
每个人都会来
回到坎普·科拉尔，
and we could play forever.
我们可以永远玩下去。
- Living all by your lonesome
didn't help your social skills
- 独自一人生活
对你的社交技能没有帮助
none, did it?
没有，是吗？
- Nope.
- 没有。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
And here's all our friends.
这是我们所有的朋友。
- Elwood?
- 埃尔伍德？
You did this?
你做了这个吗？
- And you can join them.
- 你可以加入他们。
I have one more guest to fit.
我还有一位客人需要参加。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
Phew.
唷。
There.
那里。
All that screaming should
keep the Creeper away.
所有的尖叫都应该
让爬行者远离。
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- I was wrong.
- 我错了。
I need more screaming!
我需要更多的尖叫！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Whoa!
哇！
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
- [gulps] OK,
I'm sorry I told a story
- [吞咽] 好的，
抱歉我讲了一个故事
with my back to the dark.
我背对着黑暗。
But I never canoodled,
whatever that is.
但我从来没有亲热过，
不管那是什么。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Please don't kill me.
请不要杀我。
I'm too young to die.
我还太年轻，还不能死。
I got so many more
Krabby Patties to make.
我还有很多
制作蟹肉饼。
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
[screams]
My friends are all dead.
我的朋友都死了。
[all groaning]
[全都呻吟]
No, they're not.
不，他们不是。
They're all zombies.
他们都是僵尸。
- We're not zombies.
- 我们不是僵尸。
We got bored waiting for ya,
so we had a ketchup fight.
我们等你很无聊
所以我们打了一场番茄酱大战。
- [yawns] Then we got
tired and took a nap.
- [哈欠]然后我们得到了
累了就小睡了。
- Oh.
- 哦。
That's exactly what
I would have done.
正是如此
我会这么做的。
Eh!
呃！
- Hey, Elwood!
- 嘿，埃尔伍德！
We're out of ketchup.
我们的番茄酱用完了。
- Elwood?
- 埃尔伍德？
You're the Kamp Creeper?
你是坎普爬行者吗？
- I guess so.
- 大概吧。
Yeah!
是的！
- All of this was his
blundering way of inviting all
——这一切都是他的
邀请所有人的错误方式
of us to a Kamp Koral reunion.
我们一起去参加坎普·科拉尔聚会。
- I have no social skills.
- 我没有社交能力。
Both: Yeah!
两人：是啊！
[nervous chuckles]
[紧张的笑声]
- So, uh, what now?
- 那么，呃，现在怎么办？
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
Ha!
哈!
So what now?
那么现在怎么办？
So let's party.
那么我们来聚会吧。
Hit it!
打吧！
[jazzy music]
[爵士乐]
♪ ♪
[jellyfishes buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
[microphone feedback]
[麦克风反馈]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [hisses]
- [嘶嘶声]
♪ ♪
- [chomps]
- [咀嚼]
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
[all imitating conga line chant]
【全部模仿康加线唱诵】
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- Yee-hoo!
- 耶胡！
- Woo-hoo-hoo!
- 呜呜呜！
- [hisses]
- [嘶嘶声]
♪ ♪
all: ♪ Kamp Koral ♪
全部： ♪ 坎普·科拉尔 ♪
♪ Elwood kidnapped everyone ♪
♪ 埃尔伍德绑架了所有人 ♪
♪ Kamp Koral ♪
♪ 坎普·科拉尔 ♪
♪ Now the party has begun ♪
♪ 现在聚会开始了 ♪
♪ Kamp Koral ♪
♪ 坎普·科拉尔 ♪
♪ We thought we'd be killed ♪
♪ 我们以为我们会被杀 ♪
♪ Instead we're so thrilled
right down to our toes ♪
♪ 相反，我们非常兴奋
一直到我们的脚趾♪
Whee!
哎哟！
- Great party, lad.
- 很棒的聚会，小伙子。
Uh, listen, eh, I was wondering
when you were going to show me
呃，听着，呃，我想知道
当你要给我看的时候
where me lost treasure is.
我丢失的宝藏在哪里。
Heh-heh.
呵呵。
You know.
你知道。
- You're looking at it.
- 你正在看着它。
I spent it on this party.
我把钱都花在了这个聚会上。
Didn't you get the
nickel change I sent you?
你没收到吗
我给你找零钱了？
And besides...
而且除此之外...
- Don't say it.
- 别说出来。
- Aren't friends
the real treasure?
- 不是朋友
真正的宝藏？
Noooo!
不！
- [babbling]
- [胡言乱语]
[thunder crashes]
[雷霆轰鸣]